{
    "subject": "resource/Department_of_the_Arts_and_Administrative_Services",
    "predicate": "ontology/leader",
    "object": "resource/Noel_Tanzer",
    "human_readable": "Noel Tanzer leads the Department of the Arts and Administrative Services.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9802933931350708,
            "question": "Is Noel Tanzer involved in arts and administration?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9407070279121399,
            "question": "What department does Noel Tanzer lead?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9371679425239563,
            "question": "Does Noel Tanzer work in a department related to arts?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.924204409122467,
            "question": "What type of services are provided by the department led by Noel Tanzer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9152291417121887,
            "question": "Who leads the Department of the Arts and Administrative Services?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9000937938690186,
            "question": "Name the leader of the Arts and Administrative Services Department."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.878326952457428,
            "question": "What is the name of the department headed by Noel Tanzer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8417305946350098,
            "question": "To which department does Noel Tanzer belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.769626796245575,
            "question": "Who is responsible for the Department of the Arts and Administrative Services?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5506490468978882,
            "question": "What role does Noel Tanzer hold?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Noel Tanzer leads the Department of the Arts and Administrative Services.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6043_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is responsible for the Department of the Arts and Administrative Services?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6043_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which department does Noel Tanzer belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6043_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the department headed by Noel Tanzer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6043_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6043_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6043_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6043_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6043_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6043_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6043_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6043_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6043_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6043_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6043_42.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents mention Noel Tanzer as the Secretary of the Department of Arts and Administrative Services. The text also states that he is proud of what the department has achieved in recent years, and credits the DAS people for making Public Service reforms work in their context. This suggests that Noel Tanzer was indeed leading the Department of the Arts and Administrative Services."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that Noel Tanzer leads the Department of the Arts and Administrative Services (DAS). For example, one document states, \"He [Noel Tanzer] has set up a structure under which much of it runs on commercial lines and is funded on a trust-account basis, while other parts perform their traditional public-interest functions and remain on Budget funding.\" This indicates his leadership role in the department."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}